<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="dplava.xsd" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<mdRecord xmlns="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:edm="http://www.europeana.eu/schemas/edm/" xsi:schemaLocation="http://dplava.lib.virginia.edu/dplava.xsd">
<dcterms:rights>http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/NoC-US/1.0/</dcterms:rights>
<dcterms:provenance>Washington and Lee University</dcterms:provenance>
<dcterms:isPartOf>Walker-Wood Family Papers, 1910-1975</dcterms:isPartOf>
<dcterms:identifier>WLUColl0294_b02_f050_007</dcterms:identifier>
<edm:isShownAt>https://dspace.wlu.edu/handle/11021/35518</edm:isShownAt>
<dcterms:description>This is a printout of an email sent by Eric Wilson to Rockbridge Historical Society.  The timestamp is Thursday, January 02, 2019 1:18 PM.  The subject line is, "Re-Visiting Rockbridge, 1939, A New Year's Journey with RHS, and "The Negro Motorist Green Book."  The introductory paragraphs are quoted below.</dcterms:description>
<dcterms:description>"Happy New Year -- RHS' 80th!! -- wishing you well, on this occasion to herald 2019 with the first of our journeys into the Rockbridge past."</dcterms:description>
<dcterms:description>"Over the course of the past two years, we've periodically shared these RHS-Essays:  more extended reflections that write their way into the concerns and curiosities of Public History.  Beyond notice of our RHS Programs and partner promotions, these articles reflect on relevant themes, distinct anniversaries, unique and sometimes surprising people and social patterns that shape Rockbridge history.  In framing a diverse range of topics, they've explored the interconnections of Nature and History; examined the evolution of American icnics and Rockbridge flags; reflected on the shifting history of Memorial Days, the origins of Interntional Women's Day, as well as the wartime conclusions witnessed by Juneteenth, the World War I Armistice Centennial."</dcterms:description>
<dcterms:language>en_US</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:title>Re-Visiting Rockbridge, 1939, A New Year's Journey with RHS</dcterms:title>
<dcterms:type>Text</dcterms:type>
<dcterms:subject>Rockbridge Historical Society</dcterms:subject>
<dcterms:subject>Wilson, Eric</dcterms:subject>
<dcterms:subject>African Americans -- Recreation</dcterms:subject>
<edm:preview>https://dspace.wlu.edu/rest/bitstreams/d609e7ff-6234-4ad8-97fc-37852927b243/retrieve</edm:preview>
</mdRecord>
